[
  {
    "question": "z^6 + 8z^6",
    "answer": "9z^6",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "5a^8 + 2a^8",
    "answer": "7a^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2x^3 + 5x^3",
    "answer": "7x^3",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 6a^2",
    "answer": "7a^2",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^2 + 9b^2",
    "answer": "12b^2",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2a^8 + 9a^8",
    "answer": "11a^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2x^3 + 3x^3",
    "answer": "5x^3",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "7b^7 + 2b^7",
    "answer": "9b^7",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "z^6 + 3z^6",
    "answer": "4z^6",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "8b^4 + 8b^4",
    "answer": "16b^4",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "4y^7 + 4y^7",
    "answer": "8y^7",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^8 + 9a^8",
    "answer": "18a^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "9b^8 + 6b^8",
    "answer": "15b^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^2 + 4b^2",
    "answer": "7b^2",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "9x^3 + 2x^3",
    "answer": "11x^3",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3c^7 + 3c^7",
    "answer": "6c^7",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3z^6 + 3z^6",
    "answer": "6z^6",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "9b^7 + 3b^7",
    "answer": "12b^7",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2c^4 + 6c^4",
    "answer": "8c^4",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "6a^8 + 2a^8",
    "answer": "8a^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^3 + 4b^3",
    "answer": "7b^3",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "5z^3 + z^3",
    "answer": "6z^3",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^8 + 5c^8",
    "answer": "9c^8",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "b^6 + 4b^6",
    "answer": "5b^6",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "5x^6 + x^6",
    "answer": "6x^6",
    "case": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "-9b^3 + (-8b^3)",
    "answer": "-17b^3",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-6x^7 + (-7x^7)",
    "answer": "-13x^7",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 + 2b^2",
    "answer": "8b^2",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-7y^3 + (-4y^3)",
    "answer": "-11y^3",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "3x^7 + (-9x^7)",
    "answer": "-6x^7",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-3a^6 + 5a^6",
    "answer": "2a^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-5y^6 + 9y^6",
    "answer": "4y^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-6b^7 + 9b^7",
    "answer": "3b^7",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-6x^4 + (-2x^4)",
    "answer": "-8x^4",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "7a^4 + (-5a^4)",
    "answer": "2a^4",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-5a^2 + (-a^2)",
    "answer": "-6a^2",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-8b^3 + (-2b^3)",
    "answer": "-10b^3",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-3y^3 + (-9y^3)",
    "answer": "-12y^3",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-5x^2 + (-5x^2)",
    "answer": "-10x^2",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-2b^2 + (-b^2)",
    "answer": "-3b^2",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-8a^6 + 5a^6",
    "answer": "-3a^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-9x^7 + (-4x^7)",
    "answer": "-13x^7",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "x^7 + (-2x^7)",
    "answer": "-x^7",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-4a^8 + (-a^8)",
    "answer": "-5a^8",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-9z^8 + 3z^8",
    "answer": "-6z^8",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-a^5 + 3a^5",
    "answer": "2a^5",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^6 + (-4b^6)",
    "answer": "-b^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "4a^8 + (-8a^8)",
    "answer": "-4a^8",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-8x^6 + (-6x^6)",
    "answer": "-14x^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "-6y^6 + (-9y^6)",
    "answer": "-15y^6",
    "case": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "7b^5 - 3b^5",
    "answer": "4b^5",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2 - 9x^2",
    "answer": "-8x^2",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^4 - 8a^4",
    "answer": "a^4",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3c^3 - 6c^3",
    "answer": "-3c^3",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "b^6 - 6b^6",
    "answer": "-5b^6",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "4b^2 - 5b^2",
    "answer": "-b^2",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "2b^3 - 6b^3",
    "answer": "-4b^3",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "2z^6 - 4z^6",
    "answer": "-2z^6",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "7a^2 - 8a^2",
    "answer": "-a^2",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "c^3 - 6c^3",
    "answer": "-5c^3",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3y^7 - 9y^7",
    "answer": "-6y^7",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^4 - 2a^4",
    "answer": "7a^4",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9c^5 - 5c^5",
    "answer": "4c^5",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "7z^6 - 8z^6",
    "answer": "-z^6",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^8 - 6x^8",
    "answer": "0",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "7z^7 - 8z^7",
    "answer": "-z^7",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "7y^3 - 6y^3",
    "answer": "y^3",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "y^8 - 6y^8",
    "answer": "-5y^8",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "2y^7 - 8y^7",
    "answer": "-6y^7",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "8a^2 - 6a^2",
    "answer": "2a^2",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "8z^8 - z^8",
    "answer": "7z^8",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "z^2 - 2z^2",
    "answer": "-z^2",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9c^6 - 5c^6",
    "answer": "4c^6",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3c^6 - 5c^6",
    "answer": "-2c^6",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "4y^7 - 9y^7",
    "answer": "-5y^7",
    "case": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "-7x^4 - (-4x^4)",
    "answer": "-3x^4",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "7x^8 - (-7x^8)",
    "answer": "14x^8",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-7b^6 - (-9b^6)",
    "answer": "2b^6",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-y^6 - 8y^6",
    "answer": "-9y^6",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-2y^8 - (-4y^8)",
    "answer": "2y^8",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-3z^4 - (-z^4)",
    "answer": "-2z^4",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "5b^7 - (-6b^7)",
    "answer": "11b^7",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "3y^4 - (-5y^4)",
    "answer": "8y^4",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-8a^4 - (-9a^4)",
    "answer": "a^4",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^3 - (-5b^3)",
    "answer": "8b^3",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-5y^3 - 3y^3",
    "answer": "-8y^3",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^7 - x^7",
    "answer": "5x^7",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "7y^2 - y^2",
    "answer": "6y^2",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "3a^4 - 2a^4",
    "answer": "a^4",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "6y^2 - 4y^2",
    "answer": "2y^2",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-2a^3 - (-7a^3)",
    "answer": "5a^3",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-4x^6 - 3x^6",
    "answer": "-7x^6",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "7x^2 - (-7x^2)",
    "answer": "14x^2",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "8z^7 - (-9z^7)",
    "answer": "17z^7",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "9z^3 - 2z^3",
    "answer": "7z^3",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "9b^8 - (-2b^8)",
    "answer": "11b^8",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-9y^5 - (-4y^5)",
    "answer": "-5y^5",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "-2z^8 - 8z^8",
    "answer": "-10z^8",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "2c^6 - (-7c^6)",
    "answer": "9c^6",
    "case": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "y^4 - 9y^4",
    "answer": "-8y^4",
    "case": 4
  }
]